honestbee.com 2015-03-10

# Privacy Policy | HonestBee

**LAST UPDATED** : Date of Agreement

\----- 

LifeOpp Pte. Ltd (“LifeOpp”) takes your privacy very seriously. We ask that you read this privacy policy (the “Policy”) carefully as it contains important information about what to expect when LifeOpp collects personal information about you and how LifeOpp will use your personal data.

This Policy applies to information we collect on HonestBee.com and its sub-domains about:

  1. visitors to our website (the “Site”); and
  2. users who have registered an account with us; and
  3. customers who have purchased something from us.

\----

## SECTION 1 - WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED

We will obtain personal data about you when you visit us. When you visit us, we may monitor the use of this Site through the use of cookies and similar tracking devices. For example, we may monitor the number of times you visit our Site or which pages you go to. This information helps us to build a profile of our users. Some of this data will be aggregated or statistical, which means that we will not be able to identify you individually. Please see further the section on “Our Use of Cookies” below.

When you register an account with us, you may be required to provide personal data such as your full name and email address.

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.

## SECTION 2 - CONSENT

### How do you get my consent?

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

### How do I withdraw my consent?

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at support@honestbee.com or mailing us at: HonestBee 48 Niven Road Singapore 228396.

## SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

## SECTION 4 - SHOPIFY

Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you. Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

### Payment:

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service here or Privacy Statement here.

## SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

### Links

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

## SECTION 6 - SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption.  Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

## SECTION 7 - ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION AND UPDATING AND CORRECTING YOUR INFORMATION

Subject to the exceptions referred to in section 21(2) of the Personal Data Protection Act 2012 (No. 26 of 2012) of Singapore (“PDPA”), you have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please send an email to support@honestbee.com or send a letter to HonestBee at 48 Niven Road Singapore 228396. We may make a small charge for this service.

We want to ensure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. If any of the information that you have provided to LifeOpp changes, for example if you change your email address, name or payment details, or if you wish to cancel your registration, please let us know the correct details by sending an email to support@honestbee.com or by sending a letter to HonestBee at 48 Niven Road Singapore 228396. You may ask us, or we may ask you, to correct information you or we think is inaccurate, and you may also ask us to remove information which is inaccurate.

## SECTION 8 - OUR USE OF COOKIES

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behaviour information. The information is used to track visitor use of the Site and to compile statistical reports on Site activity. For further information about cookies visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org. You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases some of our Site features may not function if you remove cookies from your browser.

Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.

  * _session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).

  * _shopify_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits.

  * _shopify_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.

  * cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.

  * _secure_session_id, unique token, sessional

  * storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.

## SECTION 9 - AGE OF CONSENT

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

## SECTION 10 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

## SECTION 11 - QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at support@honestbee.com or by mail at

HonestBee

[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]

48 Niven Road Singapore 228396

\----
